# Idan Joshua Garay

# Software Engineer

A highly motivated software engineer with a strong desire to advance to the role of principal software engineer, I am dedicated to continuous learning to further refine my skills and expertise in the field. A quick learner with a solid foundation in programming principles and techniques.

# Professional Experience

Sports Social Platform, October 2022 - January 2023

#### **Koda Kollectiv**

- Utilized the specific state management used in implementing features
- Created web components e.g. searchbar with users dropdown, and avatars for selected users.

Ticketing System, October 2022 - October 2022

# **Koda Kollectiv**

- Created web components for displaying backend data using Bootstrap
- Handled logic of back-end data
- Automated data generation for the MySQL backend using seeders.
- Modified database tables to meet the hidden data requirements, and relationships identified from the front-end.

Crisis Monitoring System, August 2022 - October 2022

# **Koda Kollectiv**

- Developed front-end components e.g. collapsible sidebar, tabs
- Created web components e.g. searchbar with users dropdown, and avatars for selected users.

Static Websites, July 2022 - January 2023

## **Koda Kollectiv**

• Shaped websites to meet the clients' requirements while ensuring responsiveness.

Covid Monitoring Web Dashboard, May 2021 - August 2021

## Virtual Byte IT Solutions

- Created graphs and charts to display Covid-related data.
- Implemented features for filtering and sorting data to help users find specific information
- Developed forms and input fields for collecting and entering employee data.

## **Education**

- **University of San Carlos** 2019 - 2023 (College)
- University of Cebu Banilad 2017 - 2019 (Senior Highschool)
- Saint Louis College Cebu 2013 - 2017 (Junior Highschool)

# **Expertise**

- + React, Vue
- + Flutter (BLoC Pattern)

+ Git Repositories

- + Javascript
- + Postman
- + Typescript
- + HTML/CSS
- + Programming **Fundamentals**

## Skills

- + Interpersonal Communication
- + Problem Solving
- + Leader
- + Teamwork
- + Attentive
- + Adaptability

## Certifications

+ Shopee Code League 2022 - Participant

## **Contact Info**



**(**+63) 993 783 6470



garayidan@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/idanjoshua-garay-1a4657176/